Visit our website for more: turkision.com
No living being was harmed
during the filming of this series.
Episode 116
Nayman is reborn every day.
Nayman is invincible.
Nayman is invincible and reborn every day.
He is cruel to the enemies.
Nayman.
You.
Prepare the horses.
We'll go.
Nayman must have gone to
headquarters and charged them.
His soldiers must have gone to the tribes.
You said what
you had to say, my Bey.
But the Beys did not listen to you.
They have been besieged.
Being right will not
save the oppressed.
We will all make up for
the mistake that was made.
But Nayman is a smart man.
If he wants to
take the tribes one by one...
He knows very well
that his army will weaken.
For this reason, the Beys
will be required to disband the armies.
Will the Beys disband
their armies, my Bey?
If what we say happens...
That Nayman divides his army...
and spread it around the
tribes to besiege them...
The beys will have no other
way to protect their followers.
My bey, will you permit me to enter?
Come in.
My Bey, Candar is in the north.
Qarasi is in the west.
They've been trapped by Nayman's army.
Beys are helpless.
As for Nayman, he left the
headquarters, my Bey.
So, Nayman might come here.
Send the observers at once.
Come on.
Your command, my Bey.
If he doesn't disband the armies...
he may
want to destroy the tribes then.
Karesi Bey and Candar Bey can't risk this.
We say that his
army numbered 40,000.
Can he be defeated?
It's all over, isn't it?
My Bey.
No.
He will ask for gold.
Then he will give them a deadline.
But Beys are forced to accept this.
Boran.
It doesn't end before we say it.
We will change the
scales on this earth.
We're not giving Nayman an inch of land...
nor any coins.
Start preparations now.
And listen to me well.
Nayman held us accountable...
and set his terms...
and you heard...
What we have heard is not a reason
for us to obey, Mother Sultan.
Nayman appeared before us after
he had campaigned, Yakup Bey.
He said that his
armies are in our land.
They are waiting for a signal from him.
You've heard it.
This is the news coming
from your assistants.
Your people are in great fear.
We were caught off guard.
He besieged me here
and attacked my people.
We should have listened to Osman Bey
at the meeting that day.
Remembering what happened
before won't save you now.
Enough of that, Candar Bey.
We will get through
this disaster together.
Since we've been trapped...
So, it's time to put your swords
down and fight with your brains.
Are you saying that there is no
solution but agreement, Mother Sultan?
Unfortunately.
You cannot fight this army alone.
And we can't secure Nayman's
orders without you.
We cannot endanger the land of
Candar Bey and Karesi Bey.
We'll agree.
The safety
of my people takes precedence...
but 150 chests of gold...
150, that's too much, Mother Sultan.
Is our strength enough
to do such a thing?
Even if our strength is not
enough to do it, it will happen.
We will make it happen.
If necessary, you will increase
taxes on your people.
They will bear this burden
for their own safety.
Gold can always be found..
...but the soul...
...I'll pay the tax Nayman wants, but...
my people are basically starving.
There must be another way out.
Believe me, Karesi Bey...
Cruelty of the Mongols...
is worse than hunger.
Konya will help your people.
Konya will help my people?
Or taxes and horses?
What shall we do, Mother Sultan?
I said what I said.
We'll get out of this press
somehow...
Learn how the tribes of Candar, Karesi and
Germiyanids will be transported the gold.
Your command, my Bey.
Shall we attack?
Yes, we will attack, we will attack.
- Get ready.
- Your command.
Come on!
My Bey, what are we going to do
after we take the gold?
They will raise taxes to get gold...
and taxes will weak people.
We will return the gold to
its wronged owners.
Well, my Bey.
Increase measures.
Put the shooters in high places.
Come on.
Your command.
Gürbüz.
Explode places around the tribe.
Maybe Nayman will set up
a game when he comes over.
Let's be careful.
Your command, my Bey.
May I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
My Bey, there's news
from the observers.
Nayman's coming to the tribe.
Nayman's coming to the tribe, huh?
Let him come.
We are always ready.
The news has reached Konya.
75 Chests of Gold and 5,000 horses...
will be secured from the treasury
of Sultan Aladdin.
And you will secure the rest.
40 chests of gold...
and 3 thousand horses from me.
Mother Sultan says the right thing.
There is no difference between us now.
Karesi Bey, do what you can.
Candar Bey, even If I
search all my tribes...
I can't find 20 chests of gold!
While Yakup Bey provided 40
chests of gold...
how will you present the 15 boxes?
Beys.
Send your messengers at once
and demand gold and horses.
We don't have time to waste
We'll secure it somehow.
Go to your rooms now and think carefully.
If necessary, we will
demand from Beys...
or we will demand a
debt from the Emperor.
But we will have it.
You will be waiting ahead.
You will attack when
the signal comes.
I'll take Frigg and burn the tribe down.
Olof.
There is news from the
observers.
Yes?
Nayman.
Nayman's about to get to the tribe.
Nayman?
What do we do now, Olof?
I told you, Frigg.
The day of reckoning has come.
You will be held
accountable for what you did.
Kill me, kill me.
No, you will not die so easily.
You will first tell us about the
poison you gave Orhan.
Then you'll tell us all the
dirt you've done in detail.
Poison?
I haven't poisoned anyone.
What a liar!
Say it, who made the poison?
Who introduced poison to the tribe?
You will say it all!
Never.
I will never speak.
You can't make me talk, Bala.
You can't force me to speak.
You're going to talk, Frigg.
You will speak and beg for death.
I...
I don't beg to live...
or to die.
But Olof will kill you without
even letting you beg.
He will come here...
and he will destroy you all.
Bala Hatun.
Malhun Hatun.
- What?
- Nayman is coming.
Alps.
Never lose sight of it.
Osman.
Commander Nayman.
Do you know what it means to be
a great person, Osman?
It is for your fame to come
before you come.
Did you hear about my fame?
The hero's bone melts...
but his reputation remains.
You are right.
But it is incomplete.
When everyone who
knows your name dies...
You won't have a reputation either.
I have the power to do this, you know that.
Yes, I know.
But I know something else, too.
Say it.
The end of the arrogant people
has always been defeat.
Of course, look, Mother Sultan and her Beys
are all defeated.
However, I, the great leader, Nayman...
I visit Osman in his tent.
What a great favor!
Please ask to prepare
the table for me, Osman.
The guest is always seated in the
best position at the table.
however, say it...
Are you a guest?
Or an enemy?
I'm going to ask
you some questions, Osman.
I will decide after hearing your answers.
Osman.
Olof.
Who is this, Osman?
A dog that will die.
You'll give me Frigg.
If you don't...
I will kill a Muslim for every
hair on her head...
If you hurt one hair of any Muslim...
Then you will pay dearly.
If you don't give me Frigg...
I will spill that blood profusely.
If you want Frigg...
Then you should hand İnegöl over to me.
You are sitting on a
property that is not yours.
Decision is yours.
Either Frigg or İnegöl.
Or I cut off your head
and bury it in İnegöl.
Osman.
I gave orders to my soldiers.
If I am no longer of your tribe...
The massacre will begin.
Marmaracık Castle
Do you hear what you're saying, woman?
What did you do?
How do you drag Frigg
into a trap like that?
Don't worry, Bey.
Frigg will not be caught.
She will not be caught!
How do you know? How do you know?
Did you think of what İsmihan Sultan
would do to us if Frigg was caught?
I know, my Bey!
I thought of everything.
Frigg knows the trap, they
won't catch her.
And I've also said
this several times.
Alçiçek made me do this.
I had no choice.
My Allah!
This isn't good.
This isn't good, Bengi.
Not only İsmihan Sultan.
What would happen if Bala Hatun found
out that you told her about the trap?
Nothing like this
will happen, Bey.
My Allah!
May I come in?
Come in, my daughter.
Mother.
Ayşe Hatun sent a message.
Frigg.
They caught Frigg.
This is good news, very nice news.
Come on, my daughter, mind
your business.
Say, what are we going to do now?
Olof wrote me a letter.
He showed his devotion to me.
For this reason, he is
under my protection.
You won't touch him.
Only I pass judgment in Kayı tribe.
Of course, if you are willing to
pay the price.
As for you, Olof...
You will not carry out a
massacre in İnegöl.
Frigg and İnegöl are mine.
If Osman makes a mistake...
Big talk.
You are very brave.
I love the brave.
But my love does not prevent my anger.
Sit in your castle now, Olof...
and think of Osman's offer.
Osman.
I will come for you.
This will be the last time you come.
The table, Osman, the table.
Olof!
Shut up.
Olof, whom you
trust so much, is gone.
Olof is gone, but you stayed here.
You can't escape from my hands.
If you want to survive, you will
answer my questions first.
Your questions will remain unanswered.
I go to the grave with my secrets.
You're going to talk, Frigg.
You collaborated with İsmihan.
And the infection was
transmitted to the people
And what about
my dear Orhan?
You poisoned him.
You will tell us about
the antidote.
And whoever brought
it into the tribe, you'll say it all.
You can never know.
If I die, Orhan will go to
the grave alive.
Shut up.
Just tell me.
Orhan.
The poison had circulated in
his body a long time ago.
He has little time left
A very short time later...
His recovery will be impossible.
His body will become as hard as stone.
He will not be able to return
to his former self.
We'll see how much time you have left.
Yenişehir
Would you permit me, Mother Sultan?
Come in, Bayındır.
I have bad news, Mother Sultan.
Frigg...
What happened to Frigg?
Bala Hatun has captured Frigg Hatun.
She is now a prisoner of the Kayı tribe.
Frigg won't talk.
If she opens her mouth...
You're going to shut it down, Bayındır.
Mother Sultan, what are we going to do?
That place is the Kayı tribe.
You can't get in, and if you get in, you
can never get out.
Olof won't stand still either.
You're will go in, Bayındır.
Do whatever you have to do and get Frigg
out of there.
You won't be alone, however...
What Frigg says matters to
Bengi Hatun too.
We will solve this.
Will you let me in, Mother Sultan?
Come in, Celali.
Mother Sultan.
Nayman.
He arrived at the Kayı tribe.
What you ate and what you
drank, let it be yours.
But tell us why you came here.
Stop, let me drink my Ayran.
Ayran is very tasty!
This is the best I have ever had.
Enjoy it.
People ride horses...
they get hungry, they
drink and they fight.
Then, they have the best gifts.
Isn't it, Osman?
But I heard...
that God withdrew
these gifts from your son.
He can't
ride a horse or draw a sword.
He can't even eat his own food.
He who knows the pain
of a wound best...
is who caused it.
If you are related to this...
Or the one who was stabbed
and wounded a lot.
I have a lot of soldiers
who have been in this situation.
They were hit with poisoned arrows.
I have no business with
these little games, Osman.
Also, didn't you arrest Olof's
wife, Frigg, for this reason?
I will not get involved in your problems.
You know a lot.
Information is the source of power.
Where is your son now?
He is having treatment.
It will last forever.
They said he was petrified.
You want to see him
walk again, right?
He will walk, Inshallah.
He will recover and rise.
Then I will grant your wish, Osman.
I can cure Orhan.
Shaman.
My Allah.
You will recover, son.
The mother's heart feels that.
You will be fine.
Mother.
What's going on inside?
Nothing happens, son.
Osman.
Come on, let's see, son.
Where are we going, father?
We're going to see Nayman's doctor.
Nayman?
Osman.
Come on.
Can this man be trusted, Osman?
What if he did something?
We tried everything, Malhun.
Don't worry.
He can't do anything, we're all there.
Kumral Abdal
will check it out first
Are you sure, dear Osman?
The world is like this, Malhun.
You can take advantage of the enemy.
and harm from a friend.
Your breath is counted, Frigg.
But if you insist on being stubborn...
I will be stubborn too.
You will talk and Orhan will survive.
I can only be patient for
Orhan's health, Frigg.
Bala.
Orhan.
He will never be able to
get back on his feet.
You didn't hit your target, Frigg.
Bala.
We found the antidote.
Thank Allah.
Now you think about the rest, Frigg.
You have nothing more to give us.
Death awaits you.
Now who's going to take
you from my arms, Frigg?
Osman.
Wait.
His condition is bad.
The poison had spread
throughout his body.
When his limbs are petrified...
and the blood flow stops the body...
he loses his strength.
There is one solution.
Say, what is it?
Say it.
Hot water.
Come on, Malhun.
Boran.
Summon Kumral Abdal.
Your command, my Bey.
Ayaz.
No.
My doctor will look at it first.
A misplaced precaution, Osman.
What could happen to your son
more than that?
You can help me.
And you can't help me.
Orhan will rise to
his feet anyway.
But what you call a precaution...
is Kumral Abdal who keeps us going.
May I, my Bey?
Come in, Kumral Abdal.
My Bey.
Kumral Abdal.
Look at this.
It's the medicine he
prepared for Orhan's treatment.
Look at it.
You.
The herb that will give healing...
expresses itself with its
taste after its smell.
It is not known.
I don't know if it will help.
But it is not harmful.
Are you sure, Kumral Abdal?
I don't know if it is cured.
But it is not harmful.
It keeps those who are
badly wounded in war on their feet...
and those who fall to the
ground with poison as well.
Trust me, Osman.
Give him.
In the name of Allah, the most
gracious, the most merciful.
O healer.
In the name of Allah, the most
gracious, the most merciful.
O healer.
Where are the rest of these herbs?
I mean, if it's going to work, it
has to be boiled every day.
Since Nayman came here alone
as a guest without his army...
He must give us the rest.
You.
Come on.
Take Orhan inside to rest.
You didn't come here to help my son.
Say what is the reason
for your coming.
Aren't they crowded, my Bey?
Yes, they are.
But there is nothing
difficult for us, Acar.
When this caravan reaches
Olof, he will have more strength.
Things will get worse then.
But we are here not to allow that.
We're here to cut off that
hand when the time comes.
Now!
Turks!
The field is now ours, Alps!
Come on!
O Allah!
Mother Sultan and the Beys
have surrendered.
There is no war anymore.
Let's say I started an attack...
How would you
defend your lands?
Tell me, let's see, Osman.
Divide your army into four legions.
First legion...
is standing behind Candar Bey.
The second...
walks towards Karesi Bey.
And...
the third...
the army which you are leading...
it...
stands facing Mother
Sultan's headquarters.
You said four.
You counted three, Osman.
The fourth legion...
is the one you hid.
There it is, it's standing here.
When Beys attack you...
you will return with
10,000 of your soldiers...
and come to where t
his fourth unit is.
And you will kill the Beys like this.
I thought you knew the Three Legions.
But you knew about the legion that was
going to attack from the rear as well.
Fortunately, there is no
need for this anymore.
Beys will bring me gold.
What about you?
You wanted to be at the head of
the army that was established.
If you were at the lead, what
would you do?
You only trust the number
of your soldiers.
But this place is our home.
We know the straits and rivers
that will stop your army.
You're going to Olof...
but tell him...
that his punishment
in these lands is death.
Did you hear me?
Go now before I kill you.
Collect the gold, chariots and
everything that is there, valiants.
We will return to the tribe.
Victory is ours!
Allah is great!
For the campaign I'm going to do...
I can say it.
You were going to divide the army
into a hundred sections...
and try to drain my soldiers.
But the thing you
overlooked, Osman, is...
You still think of yourself
as someone from the tribe.
You will lose your cities and
locations when you withdraw inside.
Quitting would have finished you off.
I wasn't going to do anything you said.
If you want to see what I do...
You should test it then.
However...
My campaigns are kept secret until then.
My Bey.
Kumral Abdal.
Orhan Bey started to feel
numbness in his feet.
The effect of the poison
is starting to stop, thank Allah.
What are you saying?
Thank Allah.
Thank you.
Thank you, Commander Nayman.
Killing a soul and
making it heal is a skill.
We have both, Osman.
I want to host you.
You are my guest for tonight.
I am a heavy
guest, Osman, can you host me?
Boran.
My Bey.
Make the best tent and the best bed.
Commander will stay with us.
Your command, my Bey.
Orhan.
Father.
I feel my legs, father.
Thank Allah.
Come here.
Mashallah.
Thank Allah, my dear Osman.
Kumral Abdal.
What's the situation?
The medicine is effective, Osman Bey.
He feels his legs now.
The poison will lose its effect
little by little, Inshallah.
- Inshallah.
- My Orhan.
When will I get back on
my feet, Kumral Abdal?
Let the poison lose its effect first.
you will stand up, Inshallah, my Bey.
He will, my son will return to
his former self.
Inshallah.
Son, you have passed another exam.
Mashallah, your heart is as
strong as your wrist.
Come on, come on, lie down like this.
Come on, lie down like this
Osman.
Why did Nayman give us the antidote?
I had told you before too.
We've never seen an
enemy like this before.
Can there be an enemy who
keeps our son on his feet?
Yes.
Nayman's intention is...
to leave us defenseless
before it overcomes us.
He makes our hearts
feel warm towards him...
and wants to
put us under his command after that.
Well, what are you going to do?
I'll give him a
corresponding answer, Malhun.
Don't worry.
He wants to hit us
in our hearts.
We will soften his heart.
Kumral.
Tell Alps to invite my Sheikh
to dinner in the evening.
And we will invite Nayman to Islam.
If it happens...
We will win a heart
this time, not a war.
What if not?
If this is not done, then the path
we will follow is known.
It is the way of war.
But I would like him to
live with us who came to kill us.
İnegöl Castle
Since Olof didn't find whoever
blew up the armory...
he must increase the measures taken.
You have to help us.
We have to get closer to Olof.
He asked for your help in getting Frigg
to convert to Christianity, didn't he?
Yes.
But Frigg must have fallen into Bala
Hatun's hands a long time ago.
By now she must have paid
for everything she did.
He will need you more now.
And he'll ask you to
pray for Frigg.
We can exploit this.
I don't like it.
Did I say that out loud?
I mean... I wanted to say...
Be careful, Ülgen Hatun.
My Bey wanted me to take care
of you, that's why I said so.
Yes, Cerkutay, yes,
I get you, yes.
As you understand, come on.
Come on, come on, let's go.
May the great Jesus protect us!
What happened?
Olof!
Turgut attacked us.
Where's the gold and soldiers?
He left no one alive.
And he took the gold.
He said he would come for you.
Osman!
Turgut!
You will pay very dearly for this.
I will separate your bones from your skin.
Their bloodshed is more important than
worship in the church, Commander Olof.
We'll take revenge on those
who stole our gold.
Don't worry.
Sister Irene.
Soldier, come with me.
Marmaracık Castle
Stop now, my Bey.
Stop now.
Should I?
The situation is very bad.
If Frigg talks, Osman will attack us.
Then, there will be no more kinship or
council, or Aktemur and Alçiçek.
We could even lose our lives
because of what you did.
Do you think that when Mother Sultan learns of the matter, will she remain silent about that situation?
I know this, tell me
something I don't know.
I'll go and talk to Mother Sultan
when she finds out the matter.
What are you going to tell her?
What are you going to say?
Are you going to tell her that you
set Frigg up?
Will Mother Sultan keep you
alive afterwards, woman?
Mother Sultan could not
simply kill me like this.
I also know what Frigg knows, or do
you think I wouldn't talk if she did?
Of course you will.
You don't even shut up.
Alps!
Did you do what
I told you to do?
The wagons of supplies have come to the
castle now and the weapons are on their way.
Alps that you requested are
coming from the tribe.
Well, be careful.
What's happening, Bey?
Why all these preparations?
You think you're smart and you're telling
me you will talk if Frigg does.
Mother Sulta will try to kill
you so you won't speak.
Do you understand now?
But it's over.
It's over, it's over now, Hatun.
Marmaracık will become an
impenetrable fortress.
Yenişehir
When will these gold
coins come?
My children are trying to collect them
as best as they can, Mother Sultan.
But, no.
We were talking about 15 chests, but
if we collect five of them, we'll be done.
The same situation exists
for us, Mother Sultan.
The sons are trying to collect everything.
But we're a long way from the
amount we need to collect.
What about you, Takup Bey?
We collect gold coins.
But we won't be able to collect all
of them in this short time.
What shall we do now, Mother Sultan?
When Nayman sees we've raised
less money for him than he asked for...
he won't show any understanding.
Even if we give him everything we have...
we won't be able to provide him with
the quantity he asked for.
Where will we find all this amount
of gold money, Mother Sultan?
We have no other solution than to collect
the entire amount of gold Nayman requested
For this reason, we will call help
from Osman Bey if we have to.
I have brought you greetings
from Mother Sultan.
And she's telling you, you must get
Frig Hatun out of the tribe immediately.
What are you talking about, Bayindir?
This snake named Frig knows
everything we've done.
- Am I right, Bengi Hatun?
- Yes indeed.
You are right, but how?
You need to figure that out.
You never leave the tents. You gave your
daughter. You've become relatives.
The difficult for us is easy for you.
Mother Sultan has a ton of soldiers.
Why does she want our help?
Ask this question to her yourself
if you're brave enough.
Resolve this matter immediately.
Bayindir.
That's not going to happen.
So, you're saying you can't,
huh Oktem?
-Yes
-Well
So, things will change.
Mother Sultan sent this.
And she said, if you can't get her out alive,
shut her up and stop her breathing.
We will do that,
we have no other choice.
Mother.
I need to leave.
Why did Bayindir Bey come?
He's just messing around, bothering us.
Don't you know Bayindir?
We're going to the tents tomorrow.
Prepare yourself quickly, come on
This is your secret then, Osman
We forge a relationship with
God through shamans.
And you do it through your sheikh.
We don't need a person to
bond with our Creator, Nayman
Every person who believes in
Allah and His Messenger knows that...
....their Lord is closer to them
than their jugular vein.
What does this mean?
This means our Creator knows each one of us,
that He is all-knowing.
He knows every step we take.
God is great. Not every person
can reach Him. Not whenever they want.
But I don't understand your religion at all.
Whenever Nayman encounters a Muslim
and draws his sword against him...
He always hears the call of
Allahu Akbar(Allah is the greatest)
I heard it, of course.
And I buried many of them, Osman.
Go on, Edebali.
Those who fall as martyrs fall for the
sake of Allah, the Most High, the Great
His mercy is wide, his wrath is frightening.
And if people saw His torment in this world,
they would submit to his greatness.
And their eyes would overflow
with tears like a river.
Fortunetaly, His mercy reaches everyone
who asks for it.
But if His people didn't
get to reach him...
...people would say "O Lord! You didn't
let me reach you...
...why are you holding me responsible?"
I cannot call it God
if everyone talks to Him.
I am a special servant of God's.
And I am the image of his anger, Edebali.
That's the difference between us, Commander.
We fear the wrath of our Lord and have mercy
on the creature for the sake of the Creator.
But you know nothing but tyranny.
You hide your weakness under the name of mercy
and your fear under the name of your religion
Don't hide.
We never hide from anyone.
Our religion commands us to
fight against the infidels until death.
It commands us to raise the sword
until the whole world is right.
We show mercy to the oppressed.
And we only make peace with
the chivalrous enemies.
So tell me, are you a chivalrous enemy?
I am the most chivalrous enemy
you'll ever see, Osman.
What do we do with
the chivalrous enemy, my sheikh?
We inform them first.
Listen.
Those are who dispute Allah’s signs
with no proof given to them.
How despicable is that for Allah and the believers!
This is how Allah seals the heart of every arrogant tyrant.”
(Surah Ghafir - 35)
Don't be so arrogant, Nayman.
I invite you to Islam.
Come and be honored by the grace of Islam.
Now that you come and
eat and drink with us...
...trust our pure intention
towards you.
And if you are going to raise your sword,
raise it for Allah's sake
And pronounce the shahada.
Where did this come from?
Why would I even do that?
We have explained the truth to you.
If you listen to us and believe,
you will be a faithful brother to us.
If you turn away from and stay as an enemy,
our sword will always be against you.
We, as our God commanded, show mercy
for those who deserves mercy...
...and punish
those who deserves punishment.
I'm tired of your words, Sheikh Edebali.
There is a magic that I cannot understand,
but I will not submit to this magic.
I will go now and rest.
In the name of Allah,
the most gracious, the most merciful
Nayman is in the tents.
Osman Bey says there is no problem,
but we still have to be ready.
We should, Konur brother, we should, but we
don't know what kind of an enemy Nayman is.
Nayman walked into the military headquarters
they had set up on his own...
...and said what he had to say to
Ismahan and the Beys.
Hhe took what he wanted.
What did he take?
He took their courage away.
And he came here with a few of his men
without worrying about his life.
Nayman is different from the others.
He thinks differently from them.
If he was like others, he would have come here
with his army and demonstrated his powers.
Nayman wants to tell us that he am strong
even if his army is not with him.
What happened, Gurbuz Alp?
-I feel sad for Aktemur Bey.
-Why do you, Gurbuz?
Our concern is one, but yours is two.
You are getting married.
We have had marriage ceremonies during wars
in the past, don't worry.
I'm not talking about that, Aktemur Bey.
You'll understand after the marriage.
Gurbuz, say what you want to say.
Bengi Hatun will be your mother in law,
that's enough.
What a pity.
I hope Alcicek isn't like her mother.
A brave man may win in the battleground,
but he loses to his wife at home.
This shall be the only loss
Aktemur Bey gets.
Thank you.
Our Lord is great, and we say, Allah is the greatest.
Those who fall as martyrs fall for the
sake of Allah, the Most High, the Great
His mercy is wide.
And his torment is frightenening.
And if people saw His torment in this world,
they would submit to his greatness.
Fortunetaly, His mercy reaches everyone
who asks for it.
And that's the difference
between us, Commander.
We fear the wrath of our Lord and have mercy
on the creature for the sake of the Creator
But you know nothing but tyranny.
Don't be so arrogant, Nayman.
I invite you to Islam.
Come and be honored by the grace of Islam.
Malhun.
- Malhun.
- My Osman.
When did you come? I didn't hear you.
I saw that you lost yourself.
You seem to be thinking of Orhan.
He's starting to feel his legs.
The medicine is working.
Of course it is, don't worry.
Come on, put a smile on your face.
It's not in my hands, my dear Osman,
my heart hurts.
Yes, I know.
I know the feeling.
I have the same.
Now that we face this difficulty,
we will hold on to patience.
I know that, my dear Osman...
and I say it to myself all the time, but I...
I can't look Orhan's face
so he doesn't see fear in my eyes.
I'm so tired.
This pain pierced your,
but you endured and did not complain.
You never showed your pain to anyone,
but I see it.
You should rest now.
You'll rest.
While you stand in the face of the whole world,
it is difficult for me to rest.
But if I stay in this position for a while,
I will have gotten all the rest I need.
You will rest until you can stand tall.
I, our son, and our tribe need you.
Nayman is getting ready to
raid our lands.
I get my strength from you.
Our son gets his strength from you too.
Malhun.
Smile. Smile so that both
Orhan and our state shall rise.
If you strike iron, it becomes a sword.
And the man is like iron.
You beat it, you crush it.
It becomes a sword that sheds blood
and kills.
Beys of this land are made of iron.
We'll beat them first.
Then we will praise them.
And we will reward them.
We will give them power.
Only then will they show their loyalty.
And they will be our dogs.
Where's Commander Nayman?
At the smelter, my Bey,
beating the iron.
Osman.
Osman, Osman.
Osman is like iron.
Don't you hear?
Osman is a tree, a great tree.
If you break him, he will dry,
and if you burn him, he will burn.
If he burns...
He's going to burn us all.
What are you going to do, Mighty Nayman.
I'll root him out.
I will kill Osman.
If he lives, I can't make anyone mankurt.
Osman will die today.
A man is like a sword,
if he remains motionless, he will rust, Osman.
I dedicate this sword to your son.
To use it when he regains his health.
Thank you.
I am here until I die, Osman.
Think of yourself.
I will gather the Beys in Sogut.
And you will come too,
and your gold will come.
I'll be there, Commander Nayman.
I will be there
Orhan will recover.
Thank Allah.
They found the antidote,
thank Allah very much
Thank Allah.
This means that snake has spoken.
She hasn't spoken yet but
we don't need her anymore.
The only reason
she is still alive is because...
she will tell the whole world about
her actions and her partners in crime
I'll make her talk and I'll kill her in the field.
Who found the antidote? Was it Kumral Abdal?
Nayman.
Nayman's healer brough the cure.
Good, good, only Allah
knows who has the cure.
He shall recover fast I hope.
Hopefully.
I want to ask something, can I?
Go ahead.
I also want to take out my rage on Frig.
My brother's blood is still on her hands.
You should have taken revenge on Olof,
whom you brought into the castle, Bengi Hatun.
I wasn't aware of that, Bala Hatun.
I would kill him today
if he faced me again.
Enter.
Let's enter.
Let us take revenge on her for those days when
she used to laugh at us and then play games against us.
You snake!
Which face are you wearing now?
Do you have another face?
You will be punished for what you did!
Bengi.
You will meet your brother very soon.
Olof will kill you all.
Don't make a sound, I'll save you.
Calm down, Bengi Hatun.
We need her.
Wait, mother.
What are you doing?
I will kill you!
Don't you, Bengi Hatun!
I will not leave my brother's blood
on the floor.
Get Bengi Hatun out, Ayse.
Come on.
Wait for it, Frig.
Your end will come.
You will drown in the blood of the innocent
whose blood you shed.
These are your last days, Frig.
Very soon I will make you confess
in front of the people and I will kill you.
You'll be the first to die
after I get out of here, Bala.
I will sacrifice your blood for the great Odin.
Shut up.
Speak, Konur.
We prepared the map, my Bey,
we located the gold.
This is Candar's way.
And this way leads to Karasi.
And Germiyan will use this
way to carry his gold.
Shall we attack each of these three convoys
that will carry gold, my Bey?
No
The road that leads to the Garmiyan
is the long way.
This is the short way.
The other way are different paths.
So, they wish to unite the gold
before the gold reaches Sogut.
The yellow corridor is where they will do it.
Konur.
You will go there.
And you will attack them and
take their gold.
As you command, my Bey.
We know how cruel
the Mongols are, Osman Bey.
When Nayman doesn't get the gold,
he will take it on his people.
It wouldn't be worse than him
getting the gold.
Neiman weighed us first.
He knows that I am at the head of
the army that will defeat him.
Because of this, he will want to kill me
after he takes the gold.
He will prevent the resistance
and frighten the Beys.
That gold will never reach him,
and nothing bad will happen to you.
Well, what about Olof?
...I will kill his patrols and
burn his convoys, but...
Isn't it time, Osman Bey?
When are we going to knock down
Ingol on Olof's head?
Having Frig on our hands
will stop Olof for a while.
But Neiman, Neiman can have him
under his control.
If Olof entered under
Neiman's command...
as Beys disengaged their armies,
we'll be stuck between them.
We will prevent this.
Olof will hear about Frig leaving the tribe.
And then, when he also comes out,
Turgut Bey will attack him.
My heart cannot bear the agony of my country
under the feet of the infidels.
- This will be over, Osman Bey.
- Thank you.
Malhun.
Mother Sultan is confused,
and their armies are divided all over.
We will take advantage of this
opportunity and get Yenisehir back.
Certainly, my Bey.
Bala is making the preparations.
We will take back Yenişehir with one attack.
Hopefully.
And I'll take part in the meeting
that Nayman's having
He wants to cut my throat.
But I will cut his.
The only thing that can save him
from my sword...
...is that if he accepts Islam.
Everyone go back to your work.
Speak, Shaman.
You vomited the thing that wormed you.
We didn't cut off the head of Osman...
...the rebel who shed Sarul's blood, and cut
off the head of the messenger we sent.
We sat at his table.
We helped his son recover.
If we don't throw his dead body
in front of his Beys now...
You forgot how things work on earth while
getting in touch with the spirits too much!
This is politics.
I weighed him, I got to know him.
I will cut off his head now.
They will fear and the heavy taxes
will break their backs.
They will kneel in front of me
and enter under my command.
Exactly as I wanted.
What if they don't pay taxes?
They will.
I will have the most valuable thing
Beys know.
If they don't pay the taxes I want...
I will erase their souls.
Goktalay.
This is your mission.
Bengi Hatun.
What is this about, Bengi Hatun?
Didn't you say we would stop?
Shut up, Esma, shut up.
You're the one who got me into this,
shut up now.
Mother Sultan ordered.
Frig will die.
I can't do it.
Rejoice, for you will kill that infidel, Esma.
Her hands are stained with the blood
of many innocent people.
Frig will die.
If she stays alive and talks,
we're all done.
Move.
Come on.
Let her eat that and die!
Come on, Esma.
Inegol Castle
What about the cruelty?
The fact that I skinned...
...the people I killed.
Cutting their ears.
Cutting their heads.
How is it stated in our religion?
It is brutality.
But the Muslim, the Muslim
are the infidels.
They must be punished.
Don't worry, nun.
I will make them taste the pain
they have never tasted before
The Muslim blood you shed
will get you into heaven, Olof.
The great Jesus will sanctify you for the
services you render to the Christian cause.
Amen.
What's going on?
Olof.
Is this your strength, Olof?
That's a pity, look at the man who was
entrusted with Andronicus' army!
Osman was talkable.
I talked to him.
You require sword, Olof.
I have to speak to you
in the language you understand.
You'll feed her, come on.
You will die if you don't eat.
So, stay hungry, it's no longer our fault
Come on, collect it
Welcome, Commander Nayman.
When you entered like that...
You pointed your sword at me.
I forgive you.
Otherwise, I would have watered
Inegol with your blood.
I have received your letter,
and your loyalty pleases me.
Because our destinies are similar.
You are lost in the chaos.
You can no longer even name
your children after you.
Genghis should have learned from you.
We are trying not to perish.
From now on, you'll only work for me.
I will do whatever it takes, Commander.
You'll wear out Osman.
You'll start with Turgut.
You will hit him at the first opportunity.
I will rip out Turgut's heart where I see him.
...I'll goug out his eyes.
Sister Irene. Get out.
You won't want to hear what I have to say.
Kam.
Give Olof a unit of Mongol soldiers.
They will swear allegiance to Olof.
And they will be under his command.
You were going to give me Frig.
I give you an army!
Isn't it enough?
That's enough, Commander.
But you were at Osman's table.
Not everyone at whose table I sit
is my friend.
And not everyone
whose table I destroy is my enemy.
Together, Commander.
We will destroy them together.
Don't fail, Olof.
I don't keep losers alive
Olof.
There's news on Frigg
They're relocating her because
we know she's in the Osman tribe
To where?
She is under Turgut's protection.
In Turgut tents.
Beautiful.
I'll take Frig.
I'll prove my sterngth to Nayman.
And he will see who I am.
Two corpses with one arrow.
Prepare our soldiers and the Mongol soldiers.
We'll go, come on.
Let's go.
Esma, did she eat?
She didn't.
She says she'd rather die to eat.
What do we do now?
There's no other way, I'll kill Frigg myself.
Bengi Hatun.
Hatuns brought the fabrics.
We chose, but come and
you take a look too.
It must be beautiful if you chose.
I just need Alcicek to love it.
They'll make the most beautiful
bridal dress for my Alcicek, right Ayse Hatun?
Of course, of course.
Everything fits on the beautiful.
Come on, let's go and see.
You are after something.
No, why would you say that?
It's over, Alcicek Hatun.
Cahit!
Abdullah!
Baykal!
Korkut!
Uyegil, come on.
They are coming, brother.
They are welcome to come.
What is going on here? Who are you?
Why do you block the way?
Turan.
Come on.
Come on, in the name of Allah.
We will not kill them,
it is enough that you arrest them.
Okay brother.
You tired us out!
We were about to kill you!
Our goal is not to kill you.
It's not.
And now the gold will go to its real owner.
You will be our guests for a while.
Cerkutay!
Come here.
Why are you screaming? They will hear now!
They'll set a trap, Olof will attack Turgut Bey,
what are we going to do now?
That Nayman or whatever his name is
gave him soldiers.
No way.
Turgut Bey had a plan.
But he must not have taken the Mongol
soldiers into account.
We have to inform him at once.
I pray that the Lord will surround
you with love in return for your services.
May goodness always be with you.
Sister Irene.
I was looking for you.
What's it?
I mean, the servants and I
were going to read the Bible.
We will start reading after
their work is done.
Read later.
Olof is waiting for you.
Of course.
Come on then, we can't keep him waiting.
Let's go.
Let's go, let's go.
Stop.
Turgut Bey.
I brought information from Cerkutay.
Come on, come on
- Turgut Bey.
- Tell me.
Nayman has given a unit of Mongol
soldiers to Olof to attack you.
They will set off soon.
Olof thinks he's a hunter.
But he will obviously become prey.
Thank you, Hristo
Thank you.
Now let's prepare a nice welcome
for that dishonorable dogs, alps!
Come on, my brave ones, come on
My Bey!
Talk.
My Bey, I brought information
from Konur Alp.
We captured the gold to go to Nayman.
Thank you.
Tell them to wait for my sign.
Your command, my Bey.
Hadrat Mother Sultan, as I mentioned before,
Frig Hatun is skillful.
She's not even eating.
If she speak, our relations with
Osman will be destroyed.
...it doesn't matter, however...
This is not the right time, Bayindir.
You understand this, right?
Frig should not speak.
She won't speak, Mother Sultan.
Never worry.
I will solve it.
If my name is Bayindir, son of Shunder
I will kill that snake called Frig with
her own venom.
Mother Sultan, Osman Bey arrived.
Let him.
Peace be upon you.
And may peace be upon you too.
Peace be upon you, Osman Bey.
You came early.
No, I came just in time.
Surely there's a reason I came before Nayman.
Where are the Beys?
The Beys have spent the night
at my palace in Yenişehir.
They should be on their way now.
You tell me, why did you come early?
No.
The palace and Yenişehir
are no longer yours.
Kayi banners are waving in Yenişehir.
O brave soldiers of the great Seljuk state!
We do not intend to kill you!
But the time has come for us
to take what belongs to us.
Now put down your swords
and leave Yenişehir.
Never! We will not leave this place until
an order comes from our Mother Sultan.
So, protect yourselves!
Aktemur.
No one will shed blood.
Arrest them.
Alps!
Sisters, let's go.
Turgut.
I came to kill you, Olof.
Shields!
Pull!
Allah is the greatest!
Oh right!
Olof!
You don't have anywhere to escape.
And you don't have any solution anymore.
It's time for you to bow down.
Now it's time to finish you off.
You are the only one to...
...bow down, Turgut.
You will kneel!
We make the mighty kneel!
And we make the one with
the raised head bow his head!
No one dares to make Turks kneel!
And you will see this now!
Ulgen Hatun is among them, my Bey.
Protect the nun.
We will break their shields.
We will slam their bodies on the ground!
Allah is the greatest!
Stand still!
Get ready!
Withdraw!
Kutan!
Protect nun Irene!
Sogut
I offered you Yenişehir before.
But you didn't take it.
And now, under these
difficult circumstances...
And while Sogut is under Nayman's threat...
Don't drive me crazy, Osman!
Nayman will not only throw a feast in Sogut.
He will seize it.
open your eyes
This is not time to rebel!
We are at war.
Because of your mistake,
we begun with loss.
From now on...
I am on the field.
I am owning what's mine.
And you won't say anything about it.
Mother Sultan.
Osman Bey, you can't pay for this!
Today we should unite!
Let's get over with this Nayman trouble.
And then we'll talk, Mother Sultan.
Osman.
Mother Sultan, the Beys have arrived.
Let them.
Peace be upon you.
And may peace be upon you.
Welcome, Beys.
Thank you, mother Sultan.
The reign of Mother Sultan has ended here.
Alps, take the soldiers to Mother Sultan.
Their lives are entrusted to us.
Thank Allah.
Kutlu, Gokluce!
Raise our banner, come on
Thank Allah, we got our palace back.
What is ours will always be ours.
Every piece of land we took
with our blood and our souls...
...will remain ours forever,
if Lord allows.
Now its ours.
And after us, its our children's.
They will carry this banner to the whole world!
They will say the word of Allah,
make everyone hear.
Our aim is to uphold
the words of Allah.
We are going to bring order to the world.
Our seeds are in Kayi tents.
And we will sprout in Yenisehir.
And then our target will be the whole world!
Allah is the greatest!
When will this Nayman come?
You want your loss to be certain, Candar Bey?
Cut it out, Osman Bey!
You did a mistake.
With one mistake...
The penalty fell on our people.
Karasi Bey.
How many people struggled?
Just because you needed to
pay taxes to an cruel.
Tell me.
As if it's not you who
caused us this trouble!
The trouble has always been here.
I just ended it.
While you were being dogs
of Mother Sultan...
I killed the cruel in Konya.
Just because of that...
...you considered me an enemy.
Osman Bey is right.
If he hadn't done it, I would have done it.
It doesn't matter anymore.
What happened happened.
The price shall be paid, Osman Bey.
Gold will be here shortly.
Who knows?
Gold may never come.
Osman Bey, no way...
I have nothing to do with gold.
But of course I don't want
the gold to get to Nayman
If a price is to be paid...
...it shouldn't be paid with gold.
Rather, it must be paid with blood.
This is the only way to equalize.
Osman Bey
If you are related to gold issue...
And if even an alp of mine gets hurt
because of this...
You will pay dearly.
Because of the mistakes you made...
...we paid the highest price.
Now...
From now on, everything goes as I say.
The army will gather again.
And the head of this army....
...will be me.
Commander Nayman has come
Let him.
I did not see my gold in the
courtyard of the palace, Osman.
Beys.
Where is my gold?
Mother.
Kasim Bey.
What are you doing?
Soldiers!
Don't ignore this cruelty!
Kasim Bey, Yakup Bey's son.
Yusuf Bey, Candar Bey's son.
Yusuf Bey...
...Karasi Bey's son.
They're all prisoners of Commander Nayman
Get out of our way!
Or else...
We will tie you behind our horses.
And we will trample you under our horseshoes.
It is clear that...
Wolves are trying to strangle the lion...
...not being aware of their power.
Have you thought the end of this, Beys?
If you are in the den of wolves,
even if you are a lion...
...one wolf is enough for you.
Osman, do you have gold?
I have nothing to do with gold.
The gold is yours and you should be
the one who knows where it is.
Why do you ask me?
Do you think you can beat me?
You try to play with me...
But there is something you do not know.
You tried to bite me, huh?
You can't even snarl at me from now on!
Son!
Commander Nayman.
I will give you whatever you want.
Just don't hurt my son.
Son, my valiant!
The light of my eyes!
Do not!
Nothing is apparent yet!
Don't make us pay with our sons!
My valiant!
Commander Nayman
Kill me but let my son stay alive.
I'm doing nothing, Beys.
He who captured the gold is the same person
that is about to kill your sons.
You will pay the price of gold
with the lives of your children.
If you don't bring me gold...
...heads will fall.
And I think that...
The reason for all this is you, Osman.
Your courage will cause your captivity.
The blood of your children will be spilled in this khan
The price for my gold is this.
Stop now!
Stop!
Don't, Nayman.
You are taking our children away
without confirming the guilty.
This is not the behavior of a man.
He who is born by the sword dies by the sword.
But Allah alone knows who will pay the price.
Visit our website for more: turkision.com